// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "An office which is run successfully shows that every member of staff works ___________",
    answer: "as a team in the office",
    options: [
      "in the office",
      "as a team in the office",
      "individually in the office",
      "in group in the office"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following of a not a reward of being truthful?",
    answer: "bad reputation",
    options: [
      "bad reputation",
      "good reputation",
      "promotion",
      "useful suggestion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The person who is the sole provider of business capital and suffers losses alone is called ",
    answer: "sole proprietor",
    options: [
      "partner ",
      "trader",
      "salesman",
      "sole proprietor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Adeoluwa bought stationary from a bookshop and pays cash. The booksellers will give him",
    answer: "an invoice",
    options: [
      "an invoice",
      "an order",
      "a voucher",
      "a recepit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The head of the state depatment is?",
    answer: "purchase manager",
    options: [
      "purchase manager",
      "sales manager",
      "personnel manager",
      "cheif manager"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "An insurance policy that covers accidents at sea is known as",
    answer: "marine insurance",
    options: [
      "fire insurance",
      "marine insurance",
      "life insurance",
      "burglary  insurance"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The following are departments in an organziation EXCEPT",
    answer: "production department",
    options: [
      "purchasing department",
      "sales department",
      "production department",
      "organziation department"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The space allowed at the edge of a document to make it more attractive is called",
    answer: "orientation",
    options: [
      "attraction",
      "margin ",
      "design",
      "orientation"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A bookseller must process all the foowing qualities EXCEPT",
    answer: "he must be doubtful in calculation",
    options: [
      "he must write clearly",
      "he must be doubtful in calculation",
      "he must be intelligent",
      "he must be accurate in calculation"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The minimum member you can find in a partnership business is",
    answer: "seven",
    options: [
      "two",
      "four",
      "seven",
      "twenty"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Creating public awareness abot the organization's product is the responsibility of ",
    answer: "purchasing department",
    options: [
      "personnel department",
      "production department",
      "marketing department",
      "purchasing department"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The book signed by people who vist an office is known as",
    answer: "visitor's book",
    options: [
      "visitor's book",
      "welcome book",
      "office book",
      "time book"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Insurer in insurance business is the",
    answer: "risk giver",
    options: [
      "insurance company",
      "agent of the insured",
      "broker of the insured",
      "risk giver"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "______ is the activities of buying, selling and distributions of goods and services",
    answer: "commerce",
    options: [
      "transportation",
      "transformation",
      "commerce",
      "warehosuing"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "An introductory card is another name for ",
    answer: "business card",
    options: [
      "business card",
      "quotation form",
      "requisition form",
      "inventory card"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a consonant?",
    answer: "O",
    options: [
      "O",
      "P",
      "B",
      "T"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "A business organzation with unlimted number of shareholder is known as",
    answer: "public company",
    options: [
      "sole proprietorship",
      "partnership",
      "private company",
      "public company"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT one of the uses of journal?",
    answer: "recording cash purchases",
    options: [
      "correction of error",
      "transfer between account",
      "recording cash purchases",
      "closing entries"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "________ type pf insurance deals with stealing",
    answer: "burglary",
    options: [
      "burglary",
      "comprehensive",
      "assurance",
      "third party"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "The method of classifying files are the following EXCEPT ",
    answer: "sorting",
    options: [
      "chronological",
      "geographical",
      "alphabetical",
      "sorting"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "The act of putting typing sheet into the typewriter ready for typing is called paper_________",
    answer: "insertion",
    options: [
      "insertion",
      "inclusion",
      "fixing",
      "placing"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Production is said to be",
    answer: "creation of good and services so as to satisfy human want",
    options: [
      "changing the form of raw materials",
      "creation of only services",
      "creation of goods",
      "creation of good and services so as to satisfy human want"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "One of the Nigerian International Seasport is in",
    answer: "lagos",
    options: [
      "onitsha",
      "kano",
      "ibadan",
      "lagos"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Petty casbook is another name for",
    answer: "minor expenses",
    options: [
      "bank transaction",
      "minor expenses",
      "staff salary",
      "credit sales"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "A place where correspondence is recevied in the office is called?",
    answer: "despatch office",
    options: [
      "personnel office",
      "despatch office",
      "registry",
      "cash office"
    ]
  },
];